<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on Explain IT Like I&#39;m 5</title>
    <link>http://eli5.it/categories/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on Explain IT Like I&#39;m 5</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 15:27:34 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://eli5.it/categories/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>pacman</title>
      <link>http://eli5.it/linux/tooling/pacman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 15:27:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eli5.it/linux/tooling/pacman/</guid>
      <description>Installing a package sudo pacman -S &amp;lt;package&amp;gt;  Searching for a package sudo pacman -Ss &amp;lt;description/name&amp;gt;  Removing packages To remove a single package, leaving all of its dependencies installed:
sudo pacman -R &amp;lt;package&amp;gt;  To remove a package and its dependencies which are not required by any other installed package:
sudo pacman -Rs &amp;lt;package&amp;gt;  Cleaning the package cache The built-in option to remove all the cached packages that are not currently installed is:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zsh</title>
      <link>http://eli5.it/linux/tooling/zsh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 11:13:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eli5.it/linux/tooling/zsh/</guid>
      <description>Install and switch to ZSH sudo pacman -S zsh zsh-completions  Run it once to configure the default settings.
zsh  Install Antigen for advanced plugin management yaourt -S antigen-git  Add the following source to your ~/.zshrc file:
source /usr/share/zsh/scripts/antigen/antigen.zsh
Add some awesome plugins like Git support and Syntax hightlighting
# Load the oh-my-zsh&#39;s library. antigen use oh-my-zsh # Bundles from the default repo (robbyrussell&#39;s oh-my-zsh). antigen bundle git # Syntax highlighting bundle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>arch linux n00b guide</title>
      <link>http://eli5.it/linux/install-guide/arch-linux-n00b-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 00:14:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eli5.it/linux/install-guide/arch-linux-n00b-guide/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites Check internet connection ping -c 3 www.google.com  If needed try connecting via WiFi wifi-menu  Check EFI vars present efivar -l  Main installation Set system time using NTP: timedatectl set-ntp true timedatectl status  Partitioning TIP: Leave a 128MiB empty ‘gap’ partition in between your ‘other os’ and your new partition.
Zap all data on disk and create a new GPT table. Show current partition table</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>